{
    "id": "c887017da964463492ca8bea86a67e7e",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Air conditioning …………………………. for a comfortable house.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is making",
                "makes",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The new hospital ……………………………… in the coming year.",
            "description": "To express simple futurity, we use the simple future. The passive form is used here because the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "will build",
                "will be built",
                "would be built"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dancing ………………………….. right after the dinner",
            "description": "To express simple futurity, we use the simple future.",
            "answers": [
                "will commence",
                "will be commencing",
                "is commencing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I went to his place yesterday, his wife ………………………….. me a cold reception.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished events in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "gave",
                "has given"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My birthday …………………………….. with my wedding anniversary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is coinciding",
                "coincides",
                "coincide"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His parents ………………………… him because he was an only child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pampers",
                "has pampered",
                "pampered"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "In hemophilia the blood ………………………. properly.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "does not clot",
                "do not clot",
                "not clot"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Pine trees …………………………. to the ever green class.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "belong",
                "belonging",
                "are belonging"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The class ……………………………. graduating in June.",
            "description": "Collective nouns are usually treated as singular.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Eggs ………………………….. according to size.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "classify",
                "are classified",
                "have classified"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Butter …………………………. by churning cream.",
            "description": "The passive verb is used here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "is made",
                "has made"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The circuit of the earth around the sun …………………………… about a year.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is taking",
                "takes",
                "has taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}